Guide to the Gary Stevenson Papers WAG.182
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Gary Stevenson Papers
circa 1948-circa 1994
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Stevenson, Gary C., 1951-
WAG.182
22 Linear Feet in 22 boxes
Gary Stevenson served as an organizer and business agent for the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 810, from 1977 to 1987. Local 810 represents laborers in New York, New Jersey, Connecticut, and Pennsylvania who work in a variety of occupations, including truck drivers, metal and machine shop workers, and lab and manufacturing technicians. The collection contains files related to the organizing efforts and other activities of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) from the 1960s to the 1990s.
Historical/Biographical Note
Gary Stevenson served as an organizer and business agent for the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 810, from 1977 to 1987. Local 810 represents laborers in New York, New Jersey, Connecticut, and Pennsylvania who work in a variety of occupations, including truck drivers, metal and machine shop workers, and lab and manufacturing technicians. Stevenson's duties for Local 810 included executing organizing campaigns, handling grievances, and negotiating contracts between union members and their employers. He later worked for the IBT in a broader capacity, serving as the union's Eastern Region Organizing Coordinator.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains files related to the organizing efforts and other activities of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) from the 1960s to the 1990s. The work of Local 810 in New York and New Jersey makes up a significant portion of the collection. To a lesser extent, the collection also includes information on the activities of the Teamsters for a Democratic Union-Professional Drivers Council (TDU-PROD) and other labor unions, as well as other local IBT unions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The provenance of this collection is unknown. The accession number associated with this collection is 1950.102.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Researchers interested in the International Brotherhood of Teamsters may also wish to consult the following collections:
International Brotherhood of Teamsters Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 018)
Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 282, FORE (Fear of Reprisal Ends) Records (WAG 107)
Robert Fitch Papers (WAG 261)
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Labor unions -- New York (State); Labor unions -- New Jersey.; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- Organizing.; Labor unions |z United States |y 1970-1990.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; Teamsters for a Democratic Union; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 810
- Inventory
  - Couriers--Other Unions: Independent Messengers Association, Independent Couriers Association, and Amalgamated Messengers Union (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Couriers--Teamsters Locals 61 and 840: Organizing Analyses, Correspondence, Workshop Manual, Flyers, and Press, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Delta Mechanics, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - National Master Freight Agreement (NMFA): Correspondence, Teamster Press, Flyers, and Mainstream Press, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement (NMFA): Research and Agreement, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Schreiber Foods, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sun Country Airlines and Continental Airlines, 1983 and 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - United Airlines: Agreement, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - United Airlines: Correspondence, 1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - United Airlines: Flyers, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines: Lists, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines: Organizing, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines: Press, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines: Proxy Statement, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines: Research--Employee Plans, 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - United Airlines: Research--Employee Plans, 1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - USAir: Background, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - USAir: Contract Proposals and Agreement (1989-1990) and Pan-Am Agreement (1972), 1972-1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - USAir: Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - USAir: Flyers from International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - USAir: Flyers from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - USAir: Flyers from the United Steelworkers of America (USWA), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - USAir: In-House (IBT) Research Materials, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - USAir: Legal--Government Documents, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - USAir: Lists, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - USAir: Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - USAir: Organizing, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - USAir: Press, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - USAir: Representation Election Cards--Signups, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - USAir: Teamster Press, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Flyers, Leaflets, Pamphlets, Publications, and Ephemera from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters and Other Labor Organizations (Box 2)
  - Chromium Planting and Polishing Employees Affidavit, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Eastern, Southern, Central, Western Conference Organizing Coordinators' Reports, June 1992 - October 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - IBT-- Research Booklets, 1993 - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Literature from Various Unions & Long Island Labor Coalition, 1987 - 1991, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local 810-- Belmet Organizing Campaign, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local 810-- Hooker Chemical: Local 810 Correspondence, Organizing Lists, Research, Union Lists, Notes and Workers' Statements, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local 810-- Hooker Chemical: Company Correspondence, Third Party Correspondence,Company Lists and Company Support, 1960-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local 810-- Hooker Chemical: Department of Labor, National Labor Relocations Board and Internal Revenue Service, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local 810-- Hooker Chemical: Local Union's 482 Glass and Ceramics Union; Local 239-H Cleaners and Dryers Union; Hempstead Civil Service Employees Association; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Negotiations and Proposals, Settlement Offer, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Local 810-- Hooker Chemical: Press, Flyers and Publicity, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Local 810-- Local 6 United Industrial Workers Union: Nevitt Sales and Corporation, 1979 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace Affidavits, 1981 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Local 810 (and 1034)-- Mattiace Petro-Chemical Company and Others: Agreements, Resolutions and Bylaws, 1979 - 1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace Correspondence, October 6, 1981 - December 2, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace Flyers, Publicity, "Coalition to Save Hempstead Harbor Newsletter", 1982 - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace: Internal Revenue Service LM-2 and LM-3 Forms, 1977 - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace National Labor Relations Board Proceedings: Roth v Mattiace (CV 860707); Mattiace v Local 810 (29-CA-1201), 1977 - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace New York State Department of Labor Actions and New York State Department of Law Indictments, 1985 - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace Press Clippings, Novemeber 19, 1981 - October 1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace Research, 1980 - 1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace Transcripts, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace: Union-Generated Lists, Notes of Gary Stevenson, and Authorizations, 1981 - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Local 810-- Mattiace U.S. Bankruptcy Court, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien & Sons, Incorporated: Correspondence, 1984 - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien (and Vaughan's Seed Company): Negotiations, Proposals, and Agreements, 1984 - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien: National Labor Relations Board Proceedings; Grievances; New York State Mediation Board; Notice of Petition State Supreme Court in the Matter of Local 810 v Van Bourgondien, 1985 - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien: Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1985 - 1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien: Research, 1979 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien: Union Lists, Authorization Cards, Organizing Materials, Safety and Steward's Manuals, 1985 - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Local 810-- Van Bourgondien: Union Press, Reference Flyers and Publications, and Mainstream Press, 1985 - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Southeastern Area/Metrolina Project: Target List and Press, 1990 - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Agreements with International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1978 - 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Agreements with Various Unions, 1984 - 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - IBT Authorizations (Miscellaneous), 1985 - 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - IBT (Gary Stevenson)-- Miscellaneous IBT Correspondence, Miscellaneous Press, and Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1984, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - IBT Press Regarding Labor, 1974 - March 22, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - IBT Press Regarding Labor, May 28, 1994 - August 28, 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - IBT Rank and File Press and Union Press, 1980 - 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT)/Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU)-- Press Clippings Regarding Teamsters, December 28, 1973 - December 9, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - IBT/TDU-- Press Clippings Regarding Teamsters, January 17, 1995 - December 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries Authorizations, 1985 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Company Support, Proceedings of Glen Cove Library Trustees, and School District Board of Education, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Correspondence, 1963 - 1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Flyers, Letters of Support, and Literature on Gender and Race-Based Pay Disparities, 1981 - 1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Job Descriptions, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Litigation, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Negotiations and Agreements, 1979 - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Negotiations and Agreements, 1985 - 1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: New York State Public Employment Relations Board, 1984 - 1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Notes of Gary Stevenson and Others, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Press, 1982 - 1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Research and Lists, 1984 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Local 810-- Glen Cove School District and Libraries: Research and Lists, 1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "The Story of Glen Cove" by Robert Coles, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - AFL-CIO Convention Washington, D.C., November 13-16, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Blank Agreements: Master Contract Local 553, Supplemental Agreement Local 355, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Court Order 88 Civ. 4486 (DNE)-- USA vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Regarding Functioning of the Convention, July 9, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - General Legal Texts, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - IBT-- Conference Reports, January 15 - April 30, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - IBT-- "Convention News" and "Overnite Organizer" (Newsletters During IBT Twenty-Fifth International Convention), July 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - IBT-- Election 1991: Campaign Literature, 1991 - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - IBT-- Elections: Correspondence, Voting Instructions, and Teamsters for Democracy Correspondence, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - IBT-- Jimmy Hoffa Campaign vs. Ron Carey, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - IBT-- Hoffa vs. Carey: Newspaper Clippings and Reprints of Articles, July - October, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - IBT-- Ephemera from IBT Twenty-Fifth International Convention, July 15-19, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - IBT-- Miscellaneous Ephemera from the IBT Twenty-Fifth International Convention, July 15-19, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - IBT-- Memos and Correspondence, 1989 - 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - IBT-- Minutes of Over-the-Road and General Hauling Coordinating Committee, September 9, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - IBT-- Organizers' Reports and Memos (Gary Stevenson, Vicki Saporta, Linda S. Brown, et al.), 1990 - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - IBT-- Organizers' Reports and Memos, 1993 - 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - IBT-- Organizing Department: Report to General Executive Board and Organizing Grant Criteria, January 15 - April 30, 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - IBT-- Report Regarding Articles XX and XXI of AFL-CIO Constitution, May 26, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - IBT-- Ron Carey Campaign vs. Hoffa, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - IBT-- Rosters, April - October, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - IBT-- Text of Booklet About the Teamsters, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - IBT-- Twenty-Fifth International Convention Philadelphia, PA, July 15-19, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - IBT-- Two Reports to All Affiliates Regarding Ethical Practices Committee Affairs and Revised Proposed Model Local Union Bylaws, October 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Local 810 (and 1205)-- Ace Shower Door, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Local 810-- Ambassador Books: Local 810, IBT Correspondence, Organizing Materials, Authorizations, Flyers and Press, Texts and Reflections, "Back Talk" No. 1-8, Sample Contract, Company Support, and Notes, 1979 - 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Local 810-- Local 28 Sheet Metal Workers International Association: Richmond Heating and Air Conditioning, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local 810-- North Shore Public School District: Correspondence, Research and Lists, Public Employment Relations Board, Agreement, and Flyer, 1988 - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local 810-- Silent Hoist and Crane: Correspondence, Research, Authorizations, National Labor Relations Board, LM-2, Agreements, Notes, and Flyers, 1978 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local 810-- U.S. HomeCare Incorporated: Research and Lists, Authorizations, and Flyer, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Local 810-- Westfield Design: Grievance Statements, Research and Lists, National Labor Relations Board, Home Visit Reports, Authorizations, Union Lists, and Flyers, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - "Origins, NC Documentary Service", 1984 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Publications and Pamphlets by IBT and Local 810, 1984 - 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU)-Professional Drivers' Council (PROD)-- Press and Flyers, 1976 - 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Arkansas Freightways: Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association, Inc. (BTOBA)-- 1981 Constitution, Benefits and Health Insurance Plans, 1981 - 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - BTOBA-- Correspondence, Endorsements from Tony Mauro, and Tributes to Tony Mauro, 1983 - 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - BTOBA-- Flyers and Special Awards Ceremonies, 1987 - 1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - BTOBA-- Lists and Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - BTOBA-- Press Clippings, 1985 - 1990, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - BTOBA-- Report of Mayor's Advisory Committee (1987), New York State Police Departmental Legislation (1989), and Calendar of Bills (1990), 1987 - 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - BTOBA-- Union Press, 1984 - 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Federal Express: Correspondence, Labor Support and Flyers, Company Support, and IBT Organizing Report, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Health Insurance Article ("Daily News"), July 25, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hertz-- Local 71: Company Support, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hertz-- Local 71: National Labor Relations Board Proceedings, Teamster Flyers, and Lists, 1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Hertz-- Local 71 (and 495): Western Conference of Teamsters: Teamster Correspondence, Authorizations, Contracts, and Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - IBT-- Pension Plan, April 1, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - IBT-- Pension Plan, 1982 - 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "Labor Notes" Conference-- "New Directions for Labor" (Conference Pamphlet), May 19-21, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Local 810-- IBT Retirement Plan, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Long Island Labor Religion Coalition (Gary Stevenson), 1986 - 1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Pony Express-- Company Support: Correspondence and Propaganda, April 13-July 14, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Pony Express-- NLRB Actions and Contract Negotiations and Proposals, 1989 - 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Pony Express-- Research, Lists, and Notes, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Pony Express-- Teamster Correspondence, March 4-December 16, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Pony Express-- Teamster Press, Mainstream Press, and Teamster Flyers, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Pony Express-- United Plant Guard Workers of America (UPGWA) and Federal Express, 1991 - 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Postal Workers Defense Committee-- Newspaper "P.O.W." (Post Office Worker) and Pamphlet "The Struggle Continues" (Address by Jean-Claude Parrot), August-September 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU)-- Convention in Ypsilanti, MI, November 2-4, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - TDU-- Convention in Cleveland, OH, October 11-12, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - TDU-- Convention in Detroit, MI, October 31-Novembe 1, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - TDU-- Correspondence, 1981 - 1982, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - TDU-- Ephemera from National Convention, November 1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - TDU-- Pension Plan Reports, 1978; 1981 - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - TDU-- Proposals Submitted to Twenty-Second Convention of IBT in Las Vegas, NV: "The Teamsters Union: New Directions for the 1980s" and Special Action Packet, June 1-5, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Various IBT Locals (Local 400 United Food and Commercial Workers) and Waban, Inc., 1992 - 1993 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Voter Registration Campaign-- Human Serve Fund, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Arkansas Freightways-- Company Materials and Propaganda, 1981 - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Arkansas Freightways-- International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) Correspondence, Research Materials, and Notes, 1990 - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Arkansas Freightways-- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Cases, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas Freightways-- Organizing Materials, Authorization Cards, and Flyers, 1990 - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Conference IBT-- Correspondence, Research and Lists, Organizing Materials, Flyers, Teamster Press, NLRB, Cox Enterprises (Staten Island Cable), 1991 Master Automobile Transporters Agreement, and Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1991 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hospital Proposals, March-May 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - IBT Joint Council 9 (Southeast)-- Correspondence, Labor Support, Research and Lists, NLRB, Litigations (Autozone), and CCAir, Inc., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - IBT Joint Council 10 (New England)-- Correspondence, Organizing Materials, Research and Lists, Labor Support and Flyers, Press, Company Support, IRS, NLRB, and Vermont Labor Relations Board, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IBT Joint Council 16 (New York): Correspondence, Research and Lists, Labor Support, Union Press, Flyers and Publications, Mainstream Press, and Negotiations and Agreements, 1976 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - IBT Joint Council 17 (West New York): Correspondence, Research and Lists, and NLRB, 1991 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - IBT Joint Council 18 (New York)-- Correspondence, 1992 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - IBT Joint Council 40 (New York-Pennsylvania)-- Correspondence, Research and Lists, Organizing Materials, Authorizations, Labor Support, Co-Support, and Agreements, 1989 - 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - IBT Joint Council 62 (Maryland)-- Correspondence and "Rank and File" Press, 1991 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - IBT Joint Council 64 (New England)-- Correspondence, Research and Lists, Organizing Materials, Flyers, NLRB, Connecticut Department of Labor, Job Descriptions, and Notes, 1958 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - IBT Joint Council 73 (New Jersey)-- Correspondence, Research and Lists, Organizing Materials and Flyers, Teamster Press, Mainstream Press, Joint Council 73 Convention Agenda, NLRB, Negotiations and Agreements, and Notes, 1991 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - IBT Joint Council 83 (Virginia)-- Correspondence, Research and Lists, Organizing Materials, Flyers, Authorizations, NLRB, and Notes, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - IBT Washington, D.C. National Headquarters and 1992 LM-2, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - JC Penny-- U.S. Public Company Profile, Financial Data Report, and Proxy Statement, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Local 251-- Rhode Island Hospital: Correspondence and Union Business, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Local 251-- Rhode Island Hospital: Flyers, Handouts and Publications, "Rank and File" Press, and Mainstream Press and Media, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Local 251-- Rhode Island Hospital: Labor Support Conferences, AFL-CIO Conventions, Company Support Materials, and NLRB, 1992 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Local 251-- Rhode Island Hospital: Negotiations and Proposals, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Local 251-- Rhode Island Hospital: Research, Lists, and Organizing Materials, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Local 251-- Rhode Island Hospital: Tentative Agreements, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Call Register, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - [IBT Roster, Record Book, and Planner], 1982, 1986, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Labor Support-- Correspondence, Research and Lists, Organizing Materials, Flyers and Publications, "Rank and File" Press, and General Press and Media, 1984 - 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Labor Support-- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), Labor Support Conferences and Addresses, Association for Union Democracy, and Notes, 1984 - 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Media Coverage of Teamsters Union, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Media Coverage of Teamsters Union (Continued), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs], 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs], undated (Box 8, Folder 8)